<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
<webSite>http://www.mline.top</webSite>
<webMaster>SAMHO Club</webMaster>
<webMaster>1400778647@qq.com</webMaster>
<updatePeri>600</updatePeri>
<item>
	<title>
<![CDATA[山合文化介绍]]>
</title>
<link>
<![CDATA[http://www.mline.top/generic-company.html]]>
</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[山合文化创意设计院简介]]>
</description>
<text>
<![CDATA[
	风云涌动，百家争鸣，世界没有比此时此刻更加热闹和变化的。如果说整个世界好比是一场大富翁游戏，那么谁掌握主动权，谁率先设计了游戏规则，则所有的人都要按照这个规则行事；除非有一天出现了一个敢于挑战权威的人，打乱了原有的规则，所有按部就班的人突然间失去了方向，不知该走向何方，是观望还是主动站队就尤为重要了。
	古有客卿，文人志士为天下大势献计献策，纷纷发表自己的言论，自己的设计方案，自己对世界的定义；现有各类媒体智囊机构，学术团体为世界的变化献计献策，评头论足。我们觉得世界本是虚无的，因为人有思想，有想象，有抱负，有欲望，所以铸就了这样一个精彩纷呈的世界。当世界再一次被打破了宁静，站在了一个十字路口时，谁会是下一个设计者？而我们身处在这个游戏中的每一个人，每一个社会团体，每一家生产经营者又将会引来怎样的挑战，又将会如何应对这百年不遇之大变局？

思维，思想，远见的高低将直接影响是否有能力抓住这变局中的机遇，而当所有的一切还未明朗时，自己有无法看清时，则需要运用外部用能力的智囊机构，咨询机构为其全面分析当下的形势。拥有高维度思维的领导者他能够看清变中的不变之道，不会被暂时的纷乱而影响自己的步伐和内心，但是多数的人却当局者迷，需要有一个外力来帮助他看的更清楚。尤其是伴随5G，物联网，区块链等技术的发展和突破，如何运用技术实现转型，蜕变和升级将是摆在所有人和企业面前的。有时候转型，跨界并不是否定当下的成果而是让其变的更好。世界是圆，不可分割，那么整个社会本就一体，它没有绝对意义上的分别，着重与一个领域在过去或许可以，但是在未来必死无疑，因此未来的企业家，个人都需要全局思维，必须是文武双全，而不是两耳不闻窗外事，一心只读圣贤书。

从来都是企业去适应时代，没有时代去适应企业的。就如《易经》否卦中所言：倾否，而非否倾。与其被封闭的局面所颠覆，倒不如主动去颠覆封闭的局面。“倾否”，不是只倾一次、一劳永逸，而是随着时代的浪潮不断地颠覆，不断地“倾否”。
岁月推着时代的车轮不停地往前走，谁也无法找到一种能在市场中长存的模式，更不能保证有永恒的竞争力，也难以肯定哪些经验是不能够被颠覆的。市场变幻莫测，又残酷至极，时代抛弃你时，连一句招呼也不会打。

山合世纪文化创意设计公司在此时孕育而生，成立之初的初心就是运用我们的所思所想所见为正在经历这场百年机遇的你我提供不一样的借鉴和更具未来性的思想。用更加广阔的视野去看待世界或许能够看到一个不一样的世界，把自己放到穹顶之上在看当下的种种或许比告诉你如何做更为重要和实用。受人与鱼不如授人以渔！
THERE IS NO MORE LIVELY AND CHANGING WORLD THAN AT THIS MOMENT. IF WE SAY THAT THE WHOLE WORLD IS LIKE A GAME OF TYCOONS, THEN WHO HAS THE INITIATIVE AND WHO HAS DESIGNED THE RULES OF THE GAME FIRST, THEN ALL PEOPLE SHOULD ACT ACCORDING TO THIS RULE; UNLESS ONE DAY A PERSON WHO DARES TO CHALLENGE THE AUTHORITY BREAKS THE ORIGINAL RULES, ALL THE PEOPLE ON DUTY SUDDENLY LOSE THEIR DIRECTION AND DON'T KNOW WHERE TO GO AND WHETHER TO WAIT OR TAKE THE INITIATIVE TO STAND IN LINE THAT'S ESPECIALLY IMPORTANT.

IN ANCIENT TIMES, THERE WERE KE QING, SCHOLARS WITH LOFTY IDEALS, WHO MADE SUGGESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS FOR THE GENERAL SITUATION OF THE WORLD, PUBLISHED THEIR OWN OPINIONS, THEIR OWN DESIGN SCHEMES, AND THEIR OWN DEFINITIONS OF THE WORLD; AT PRESENT, VARIOUS MEDIA THINK TANKS AND ACADEMIC GROUPS HAVE PROVIDED SUGGESTIONS AND COMMENTS FOR THE CHANGES OF THE WORLD. WE FEEL THAT THE WORLD IS NOTHING, BECAUSE PEOPLE HAVE IDEAS, IMAGINATION, AMBITION AND DESIRE, SO WE HAVE CREATED SUCH A WONDERFUL WORLD. WHEN THE WORLD IS ONCE AGAIN BROKEN, STANDING AT A CROSSROADS, WHO WILL BE THE NEXT DESIGNER? AND WE ARE IN THIS GAME, EVERY PERSON, EVERY SOCIAL GROUP, EVERY PRODUCER AND OPERATOR WILL LEAD TO WHAT KIND OF CHALLENGES, AND HOW WILL WE DEAL WITH THIS ONCE-IN-A-CENTURY GREAT CHANGE?

THE LEVEL OF THINKING, THINKING AND FORESIGHT WILL DIRECTLY AFFECT WHETHER THEY HAVE THE ABILITY TO SEIZE THE OPPORTUNITIES IN THE CHANGING SITUATION. WHEN ALL THE THINGS ARE NOT CLEAR AND YOU CAN'T SEE THEM CLEARLY, YOU NEED TO USE EXTERNAL THINK TANKS TO COMPREHENSIVELY ANALYZE THE CURRENT SITUATION FOR THEM. A LEADER WITH HIGH-DIMENSIONAL THINKING CAN SEE THE UNCHANGING WAY IN THE PROCESS OF CHANGE, AND WILL NOT BE AFFECTED BY THE TEMPORARY CHAOS. HOWEVER, MOST PEOPLE ARE LOST IN THE GAME AND NEED AN EXTERNAL FORCE TO HELP HIM SEE MORE CLEARLY. ESPECIALLY WITH THE DEVELOPMENT AND BREAKTHROUGH OF 5G, INTERNET OF THINGS, BLOCKCHAIN AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES, HOW TO USE TECHNOLOGY TO REALIZE TRANSFORMATION, TRANSFORMATION AND UPGRADING WILL BE PLACED IN FRONT OF ALL PEOPLE AND ENTERPRISES. SOMETIMES, CROSSOVER IS NOT TO DENY THE CURRENT ACHIEVEMENTS, BUT TO MAKE THEM BETTER. THE WORLD IS ROUND AND INSEPARABLE, SO THE WHOLE SOCIETY IS ONE, AND IT HAS NO ABSOLUTE DIFFERENCE. IT MAY FOCUS ON ONE FIELD IN THE PAST, BUT IT WILL DIE IN THE FUTURE. THEREFORE, FUTURE ENTREPRENEURS AND INDIVIDUALS NEED TO THINK GLOBALLY, AND THEY MUST BE BOTH LITERATE AND MARTIAL ARTS, INSTEAD OF BEING DEAF TO THINGS OUTSIDE THE WINDOW AND READING ONLY THE BOOKS OF SAGES AND SAGES.

ENTERPRISES ALWAYS ADAPT TO THE TIMES, AND THERE IS NO ERA TO ADAPT TO ENTERPRISES. JUST AS THE NO HEXAGRAM IN THE BOOK OF CHANGES SAYS: INCLINE NO, NOT NO INCLINE. INSTEAD OF BEING SUBVERTED BY THE CLOSED SITUATION, IT IS BETTER TO TAKE THE INITIATIVE TO SUBVERT THE CLOSED SITUATION. &#IT IS NOT ONLY FOR ONCE, ONCE AND FOR ALL, BUT ALSO CONSTANTLY SUBVERTED WITH THE TIDE OF THE TIMES;.
YEARS PUSH THE WHEEL OF THE TIMES AND KEEP MOVING FORWARD. NO ONE CAN FIND A MODEL THAT CAN SURVIVE IN THE MARKET FOR A LONG TIME, LET ALONE GUARANTEE THE ETERNAL COMPETITIVENESS, AND IT IS DIFFICULT TO BE SURE WHICH EXPERIENCE CAN NOT BE SUBVERTED. THE MARKET IS UNPREDICTABLE AND CRUEL. WHEN THE TIMES ABANDON YOU, YOU WON'T EVEN SAY HELLO.

SHANHE CENTURY CULTURAL AND CREATIVE DESIGN COMPANY WAS BORN AT THIS TIME. AT THE BEGINNING OF ITS ESTABLISHMENT, ITS ORIGINAL INTENTION WAS TO PROVIDE DIFFERENT REFERENCE AND MORE FUTURE THINKING FOR YOU AND ME WHO ARE EXPERIENCING THIS CENTURY'S OPPORTUNITY. < / STRONG > LOOKING AT THE WORLD WITH A BROADER PERSPECTIVE MAY BE ABLE TO SEE A DIFFERENT WORLD. PUTTING YOURSELF ON TOP OF THE DOME MAY BE MORE IMPORTANT AND PRACTICAL THAN TELLING YOU HOW TO DO IT. IT'S BETTER TO TEACH PEOPLE TO FISH THAN TO RECEIVE PEOPLE AND FISH!
]]>
</text>
<image>
<![CDATA[]]>
</image>
<keywords>
<![CDATA[设计,咨询,报告,Design,远程工作,招聘,art,艺术,work,job,山合,商业合作,企业介绍]]>
</keywords>
<category>
<![CDATA[设计创意工作室]]>
</category>
<author>
<![CDATA[]]>
</author>
<source>
<![CDATA[山合文化]]>
</source>
<pubDate>2020-12-16 10:29</pubDate>
</item>
</document>
